Maikel Severins

IT Professional

SUMMARY

Hello, I'm Maikel Severins.

I like to solve brain teasing problems in the field of IT.

I'd like to describe myself as a fast learner;

I am confident in delivering the perfect improvements and solutions for your organisation.

Some workload that I can provide:

- Build CI/CD pipelines
- IaC with terraform/terragrunt
- Provisioning with ex. Ansible, chef, puppet, saltstack

Q: Schijfweg-zuid 5, 5995 BD, Kessel, Limburg, Netherlands

📞: +31 (0)6 ask me

: https://severinsm.github.io/

: severinsm

⇔: severinsm

in: Maikel Severins

Experience

2022 - present

Owner / Freelancer in IT at SagaOne IT

I am like a swiss army knife in IT, I'm available to freelance for different kind of IT jobs.

- Freelance IT assignments
- Infa & IT solutions
- Cyber security assignments
- Cloud engineering

2021 - present

DevOps Engineer at VidaXL

Keep the operations between development and ideas. Git, terraform, ansible, CI/CD, docker, k8, IaC, etc.

- · GCP cloud engineering
- Developing cloud functions to help with integrations
- Data transformations in python and ETL tooling

Cloud solutions

GCP - Google Cloud :

Digital Ocean: MS Azure: **★★☆**

AWS - Amazon: **★★☆**

Education

2021

Certified Ethical Hacker CEH-V10

血

2020

VHL - Virtual hacking labs

Advanced +

VOIP - Hipper basis

2013

CCNA

2012

MCSA: Windows 7 - Enterprise **Desktop Support Technician (70-**680)





2020 - present

System administrator at OMS Grashoek

SHMMARY

KVM, Cisco, Juniper, Windows server, cloudflare, terraform, Azure, O365, Dell Wyse, Active directory etc.

- Maintain on-prem serverpark
- Developing of ansible orchestration
- Maintain Azure environment (exchange, intune, autopilot etc.)
- Modern backup

2020 – present

security analyst at Cybrhat

- Co-Owner of a company specializing in cyber security.
- Red Teaming (pentesting, phishing etc.)
- Cyber Security consultancy

2014 - 2021

Sysadmin at EyeXS B.V.

SUMMARY

Development of new IT services, Datacenter activities, IT infra, consulting and many more.

- Build and maintain VDI solution A-Z
- Managing and expand Datacenter
- Customer solutions migrations
- 3th line support for very complex problems
- Taking care of the complete IT customer solutions

2007 - 2013

student sidejob at Snackbar t Strotje

SUMMARY

Side job when I went to school.

2012 - 2014

Intern & summer-job at Laurentius ziekenhuis Roermond.

- Day to day operations
- · PC and server management

2006 - 2010

Greenhouse employee at Gubbels Paprika's (Peppers)

SUMMARY

Side job when I went to school. Eventually worked 1 year fulltime after mid-school

- harvesting Peppers
- sorting Peppers
- Greenhouse maintenance

1996 - 2004

Elementary Education at Elementary school 'De Merwijck'

in Kessel

2004 - 2009

HAVO – Senior general secondary education at 'Bouwens van der BoijeCollege' in Panningen

- secondary general education
- N&T profile (Physics and Biology)
- Math A
- Biology
- Chemistry
- M&O(management and Organisation)
- dropped out in 4th class, certificate is equivalent of VMBO-T

2010 - 2012

MBO - vocational college: employee system administrator (level 3) at 'GildeOpleidingen'

- PC assembly
- Hands-on workshop

in Roermond

 same other courses as in level 4 (see below)

2012 - 2014

MBO - vocational college: System administrator (level 4) at 'GildeOpleidingen' in Roermond

- ITIL
- MCITP
- Cisco
- Dutch, English, Math
- Long internship since assignments was building complete production ready VDI solution

